GPT6 Astra for free!
I thought this was fake until I actually tried it myself.
Here's how to get this free promotion while it lasts.
I'm Ben Gersburg. I'm a Stanford founder of an AI startup.
We've raised $4 million. Go to this website.
It's a YC funded startup that does model routing.
Go to the models, you'll see Astra listed here.
You can also get other models like Claude,
Fable 5.1, all for free.
Click on Astra or whatever model you want to try.
On the right where it says quick start,
click create an API key, give it a name,
and then click create key.
That's it! Now you can use that API key to access GPT6 for free.
Try it and let me know what you build.
I'm Ben Gushberg. Follow me for more on AI founder, life, and leadership.